# **Raymond Alake**

London, SE16 2BU

Contacts: 07732395796 | ralake95@gmail.com

Profiles: www.linkedin.com | github.com

Exceptionally creative and dependable Web developer with two years' experience in designing and developing modern Web platforms and sites. Superb work ethic and strong team players. Proficient in current JavaScript framework and libraries, alongside toolset of design applications.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Hiveli, Frontend Developer / UI

2016 - Present, London

- Developed a dynamic, secure website from inception, mainly utilising HTML, CSS / SASS, JavaScript, and AngularJS.
- Designed and developed company's styleguide to ensure consistent theme on production site.
- Maintained effective communication with backend developer to ensure requirements and deadlines are met.
- Ensured compatibility / responsiveness of applications on all major platforms and browsers.

# **MoChunks**, Frontend Developer / UX

Aug 2017 - Oct 2017, London

- Designed and implemented a dynamic, visually appealing, user-friendly interface with interactive features to optimise traffic and UX.
- Communicated with client, outlined their needs and measured timeline of application.
- Provided ongoing maintenance for production site.

## **INTERESTS**

When I am not coding, studying, or pushing pixels, you will find me working out at the gym or catching some much-needed rest.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, HTML 5, CSS, CSS 3, SASS, JavaScript (client-side), TypeScript, ES6, Angular Material, Angular 5, NgRX, Angular JS, Bootstrap 4, BEM, TDD / BDD, Jasmine, Karma, Git, GitHub, Chrome Developer Tools, Responsive Web Design/Development (mobile first), UI / UX design, Affinity Graphic Design, Pair Programming, Cloud9, Visual Studios, Webstorm IDE.

- Project management with Trello & Freedcamp.
- High verbal and written communication skills.
- Profound creative and analytical problemsolving and troubleshooting skills.

### **EDUCATION**

## **Lancaster University**

Economics BSc Hons: 2014 to 2018.

### **PROJECTS**

#### Circlearn

August 2018

A grade and timetable organisational tool that helps university students remain on top of work, grades and social life.